[Music]
We all know that work,
in any form, has a
significant impact on
everyone's mental and physical health. At Prudential,
we know that the workspace is
very important because it is where
positive energy is created and retained each
day. Therefore,
we pay close attention to every
detail that affects our employees, from physical to mental well-being.
From commuting to the office, the
bus routes are carefully planned.
The radio announces bus schedules and departure times
to ensure that employees in all areas
can travel conveniently. Call
center staff
help customers answer
questions and also face significant
mental pressure, especially during peak times.
[Music]
Therefore, the space in this area is
designed as a colorful playground
to relieve stress and
regenerate positive energy.
[Music]
Or a relaxing coffee area for
chatting and motivating each other. The
tables and chairs are also
meticulously selected.  Suitable for the
diverse physical needs and preferences
of each employee,
interspersed with work-related amenities,
recreational games, or
books, this space will help each
employee relax, unwind, and open their
worldview to new ideas.
[Music]
[Applause]
For those away from home,
break times or physical exercise sessions
will help maintain both physical and
mental well-being. A
dedicated area for mothers and babies provides
peace of mind during summer days
or when young children need to be close to their mothers,
and there's also an area for the unspoken
but essential needs of mothers.
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
Attention to detail ensures
that the workplace is always a haven
for each employee. Thank you to the
security team for their unwavering efforts and for
maintaining a positive spirit to do the
right thing for our customers.
[Music]
Prudential next